

STUTI BHADAURIA

stutibhadauria28@gmail.com



B1122 Anand nagar, Gwalior



Stuti-Bhadauria-Linkedin5



Student Institute of Technology and Management, Gwalior

SUMMARY

Hello, It's fantastic to hear about my journey and my passion for full-stack development! my introduction truly highlights your enthusiasm and dedication to the field of technology. my experience with various projects and your proficiency in a range of technologies, including React, Node.js, Express, and MongoDB, demonstrates a well-rounded skill set that's essential for a successful full-stack developer.

Keep up the excellent work, and I'm sure my passion and dedication will lead me to even greater heights in the ever-evolving landscape of technology. Best of luck with my studies, projects, and future endeavors as a full-stack developer!

EDUCATION

Institute of Technology and Management

Computer Science 2020-2024 Grade-8.39

City Central Higher Secondary School

2019-2020 Grade-8.73

City Central Higher Secondary School

2017-2018 Grade-7.89

SKILLS

Languages: C++, java, Javascript, HTML+CSS

Libraries: C++, ReactJs

Web Dev Tools: Nodejs , VScode , Github Frameworks: ReactJs , Bootstrap , ExpressJs Cloud/Databases: MongoDB , Relational

Database(mySql)

Relevent Coursework: Operating Systems, Object Oriented Programming, Database Management System, Software Engineering.

Areas of Interest: Web Design and Development Soft Skill,full-Stack

CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS Cloud Virtual Internship (online)
- Web Development

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

Pninfosys | March 2023-Aug 2023

- Developed a full-stack MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js) application for a live blog.
- Utilized Node.js for backend development, Express for API routing, MongoDB for database storage, and React for frontend development.
- Implemented authentication and authorization with JSON Web Tokens

Web designing

Pninfosys | july 2022-sept 2022

- Developed responsive live website, utilizing front-end development skills..
- Enhanced UX/UI designs; actively contributed to improving code and debugging processes.
- Utilized creative problem-solving skills to reach desired goals.
 Mastered HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various development tools.

PROJECT

Login portal

<u>Using the express.js,node.js and mongodb to create a dynamic website.</u>

https://admissionportal-g888.onrender.com

Blog Project

Implemented a range of operations for blog, such as adding, editing, and deleting blogs • Utilized HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and express to create an interactive user interface

https://blog-dy19.onrender.com

Coffee Website

Created a fully responsive_ static website with react https://cocoffeewebsite.netlify.app